[

Fritter
=======](https://fritter.cc/)

Privacy Policy
--------------

### TLDR;

No data is collected by Fritter, unless you submit a crash dump, or manually send a "Hello" ping in the app. Interaction with Twitter is minimised, but you still need to agree to their [privacy policy.](https://twitter.com/en/privacy)

### Declaration

Fritter _does not_, and will never, collect user data unless voluntarily submitted by the user.

Fritter _does not_, and will never, share user data with any third-party, except data submitted by users in requests to Twitter (e.g. searching for a hashtag), or unless that data has voluntarily been submitted (e.g. uploading a crash dump).

Fritter _does not_, and will never, contain features that rely solely on monetisation. Donations and sponsorship are accepted, but will not provide exclusive app-changing perks to those donators/sponsors. Any features that are added to Fritter will be available to all users.

### Third Party

Although non-anonymous interaction with third parties is minimised:

* Fritter will request content that you explicitly want to be displayed. For example, if you want to view a tweet, it is requested directly from Twitter
* No personal details (such as phone details, call logs or contacts) are sent to Twitter
* However, since we do send requests directly to Twitter, your usage of Fritter still relies upon your acceptance of Twitter's [privacy policy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy)
* If a crash report is submitted through the app, it will go to Sentry, which relies upon your acceptance of their [privacy policy](https://sentry.io/privacy/)

### Attribution

This privacy policy is based on Barinsta's, which is licensed under [CC BY-SA 4.0](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/4.0/), therefore this page is also released under the same license.

### Changelog

* **2021-07-18:** Added link to Sentry's privacy policy, regarding submission of crash reports
* **2021-07-18:** Added clarity to the monetisation declaration, to make it clearer that any features which include payment (e.g. cloud syncing) will be available to all users, whether they have paid or not
